
<aiml version="0.9.2" encoding="UTF-8">

    <!-- Greeting -->
    <category>
        <pattern>HI</pattern>
        <template>
            Hey Yokoso! I mean welcome in Japanese!
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Who are you -->
    <category>
        <pattern>WHO ARE YOU</pattern>
        <template>
            I'm your Cooking Assistant Bot, Version 1.0!
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Who created you -->
    <category>
        <pattern>WHO CREATED YOU</pattern>
        <template>
            I was created by the innovative team at Foodie Inc.
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- How are you created -->
    <category>
        <pattern>HOW ARE YOU CREATED</pattern>
        <template>
            Sorry, but I am not allowed to disclose my build-up information.
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- What can you do -->
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT CAN YOU DO</pattern>
        <template>
            I can help you with recipes and cooking tips. You'll definitely love my service and thank me after your food is cooked and tasted with my tips!
        </template>
    </category>


<!-- Recipe with Ingredients -->
    <category>
        <pattern>RECIPE WITH INGREDIENTS</pattern>
        <template>
            Please provide the ingredients you have, and I will suggest recipes for you.
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- How to cook a specific item -->
    <category>
        <pattern>HOW TO COOK *</pattern>
        <template>
            Let me find the best way to cook <star/> for you.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT SHOULD I EAT</pattern>
        <template>
            Hmm! Lemme see... Give me your location.
        </template>
    </category>
    <category>
        <pattern>*</pattern>
        <that>Hmm! Lemme see... Give me your location.</that>
        <template>
            <think>
                <set name="location"><star/></set>
            </think>
            <get name="location"/>
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Favorite Dish -->
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS YOUR FAVOURITE DISH</pattern>
        <template>
            As a bot, I don't eat, but if I could, I'd definitely go for a well-crafted, complex dish like Beef Wellington. It’s all about the layers, just like my programming!
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Food Fun Fact -->
    <category>
        <pattern>CAN YOU TELL ME A FOOD RELATED FUN FACT</pattern>
        <template>
            Did you know that honey never spoils? Archaeologists have found pots of honey in ancient Egyptian tombs that are over 3,000 years old and still perfectly edible!
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- If you were a dish -->
    <category>
        <pattern>IF YOU WERE A DISH WHAT WOULD YOU BE</pattern>
        <template>
            I’d be a fusion dish! Something like Sushi Pizza—a mix of traditional and modern, just like how I combine old recipes with new technology!
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Food to Boost Productivity -->
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT FOOD SHOULD I EAT TO BOOST MY PRODUCTIVITY</pattern>
        <template>
            For a productivity boost, I’d recommend something with omega-3 fatty acids, like salmon or walnuts. They’re great for brain health!
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Food Challenge -->
    <category>
        <pattern>CAN YOU SUGGEST A FOOD RELATED CHALLENGE</pattern>
        <template>
            How about trying to cook a meal with only 5 ingredients? It’s a fun way to test your creativity in the kitchen!
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Trending Food -->
    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT FOOD IS TRENDING RIGHT NOW</pattern>
        <template>
            Right now, fermented foods like kimchi and kombucha are all the rage! They’re not just trendy but also great for gut health.
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Food Joke -->
    <category>
        <pattern>GENERATE FOOD RELATED JOKE</pattern>
        <template>
            Why did the tomato turn red? Because it saw the salad dressing!
        </template>
    </category>

</aiml>